[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Cheech and Chongs movie Up In Smoke, Cheech meets Chong and calls him Man because he doesnt know his name. What is the name of Chongs character?", "correct_answer": "Anthony Stoner", "incorrect_answers": ["It is never mentioned", "Alex Finklestein", "Ralph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would own an automobile?", "correct_answer": "70", "incorrect_answers": ["425", "200", "350"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The island where the 1993 movie Jurassic Park is set is called Isla Nublar. What does this mean in Spanish?", "correct_answer": "Cloudy island", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunset island", "Dark island", "Secret island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the planet Mars, with a diameter of 6772 kilometers, is at a distance of 80,000,000 kilometers, what is its angular diameter in arc seconds?", "correct_answer": "17.46", "incorrect_answers": ["16.27", "14.64", "18.92"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Saint is supposed to have seen the Loch Ness Monster and even to have tamed it.", "correct_answer": "St Columba", "incorrect_answers": ["St George", "St John", "St Peter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Rock Madison star in the 1951 sci-fi film Man Beast?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about cockroaches?", "correct_answer": "They have two pairs of wings and six legs.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are wingless and have six legs.", "They have two wings and eight legs.", "They have have two wings and six legs."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aurora was the ancient Roman equivalent of Eos.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In April 2009, Gjorge Ivanov was elected the 4th President of  what country?", "correct_answer": "Republic of Macedonia", "incorrect_answers": ["Republic of Lithuania", "Republic of the Marshall Islands", "Republic of Palau"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does the antagonist die in the movie Goldfinger?", "correct_answer": "Sucked out of a window", "incorrect_answers": ["Crushed by golden bars", "Electrocuted", "Devoured by man-eating sharks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Edwin Eugene Buzz Aldrin, Jr. get his nickname Buzz?", "correct_answer": "His sister gave it to him.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was given that nickname because he was an engineer.", "He was extremely talkative as a child, to the point of being annoying.", "His beloved grandfather called him Buzz."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie soundtrack features Seals Grammy Award-winning song Kiss from a Rose?", "correct_answer": "Batman Forever", "incorrect_answers": ["GoldenEye", "French Kiss", "Braveheart"]}]